I'm still live and here are some updates.
I'm still in Gaza City, where the ground invasion continues to intensify and get worse every
day.
Non-stop bombing, drones, we're hearing a lot more helicopters.
And just yesterday, the Zionist military, the tanks, got all the way to Al-Yazji Bakery,
which is in northern Talalhava neighborhood.
And they also were very close to Al-Shifa, so close that they started blocking the patients
from entering Al-Shifa.
Now there are still medical workers and patients, but they were trying to force them out yesterday.
They ended up retreating a bit, but they are in Gaza City.
They continue to close in and steal more and more every day with this ground invasion.
And they continue to push resources and forcibly displace Gazans to the south.
This is their plan.
And something really important to note is that the Israeli occupation forces plan to retake
the Net-Sarim corridor, cutting off the south from the north.
And so we are forcibly evacuating as the situation continues to get worse in the north with less
resources and less medical services because they keep on attacking the remaining hospital
facilities.
So we need to continue uplifting what is happening and demand a permanent ceasefire.